Guide to the C-SPAN records, 1809, 1978-2012
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center
- Series 8: Executive Files and Correspondence (Boxes 229-402), 1976-2009
  - C-SPAN's Role in Providing Citizens Information, June 23, 2000 (Box 298, Folder 8)
  - Letters Received by Brian Lamb-Part 1, 2000s (Box 298, Folder 9)
  - Letters Received by Brian Lamb-Part 2, 2000s (Box 298, Folder 10)
  - Interview with Brian Lamb, March, April 2003 (Box 298, Folder 11)
  - Venue Information-Museum and Hotels, 2000s (Box 298, Folder 12)
  - Medal of Freedom Notes, 2007 (Box 298, Folder 13)
  - Impeachment Handbook and Politician Stressball, 1990s (Box 298, Folder 14)
  - Booknotes 3 Communications, 2001 (Box 299, Folder 1)
  - Booknotes Press Hits, 2003 (Box 299, Folder 2)
  - Book Publicists, 2001 (Box 299, Folder 3)
  - Booknotes Souvenirs and Markers, 2003 (Box 299, Folder 4)
  - Booknotes 3 Book Tour Post Mortem, 2001 (Box 299, Folder 5)
  - Grant's Tomb: Robin Scullin Correspondence, 2003 (Box 299, Folder 6)
  - Purdue School of Liberal Arts Keychain, circa 2000s (Box 299, Folder 7)
  - American Writers II-Press, circa 2000s (Box 299, Folder 8)
  - Booknotes 3 Press Kit, 2001 (Box 299, Folder 9)
  - All Network Marketing, 2001 (Box 299, Folder 10)
  - Booknotes 3 Q and A 2001, circa 2000s (Box 299, Folder 11)
  - Booknotes 3 Website, 2001 (Box 299, Folder 12)
  - Booknotes 3 30 Second Spot, 2001 (Box 299, Folder 13)
  - Booknotes 3 Budget, 2001 (Box 299, Folder 14)
  - Booknotes 3 Media Relations Strategy, 2001 (Box 299, Folder 15)
  - American Writers-Ralph Waldo Emerson, 2001 (Box 299, Folder 16)
  - American Writers-Sojourner Truth, 2002 (Box 299, Folder 17)
  - American Writers II-Various Authors, 2002 (Box 299, Folder 18)
  - American Writers II-Ernie Pyle, 2002 (Box 300, Folder 1)
  - American Writers II-Ayn Rand, 2002 (Box 300, Folder 2)
  - American Writers II-Faulkner, 2002 (Box 300, Folder 3)
  - American Writers II-Steinbeck, 2002 (Box 300, Folder 4)
  - American Writers II-Hemingway, 2002 (Box 300, Folder 5)
  - American Writers II-F. Scott Fitzgerald, 2002 (Box 300, Folder 6)
  - American Writers II-Mencken, "A Man of Letters,", 2002 (Box 300, Folder 7)
  - American Writers II-Live from Harlem, 2002 (Box 300, Folder 8)
  - American Writers II-Ernie Pyle Communications, 2002 (Box 300, Folder 9)
  - American Writers II-Press Hits, 2002 (Box 300, Folder 10)
  - Booknotes 3-Radio Rounds, 2001 (Box 300, Folder 11)
  - Booknotes 3 Planning, 2002 (Box 300, Folder 12)
  - Booknotes Tour Requests, 2002 (Box 300, Folder 13)
  - Booknotes 3-TV Sat Tour, 2001 (Box 300, Folder 14)
  - Booknotes 3-Blurbs and Quotes for Tour, 2001 (Box 300, Folder 15)
  - Booknotes 3-Goals and Strategies, 2001 (Box 300, Folder 16)
  - Booknotes 3-Actual Tour, 2001 (Box 300, Folder 17)
  - American Writers-Theodore Roosevelt, 2002 (Box 300, Folder 18)
  - American Writers-Upton Sinclair, 2002 (Box 300, Folder 19)
  - American Writers-Edith Wharton, 2002 (Box 300, Folder 20)
  - American Writers-Henry Adams, July 27, 2003 (Box 300, Folder 21)
  - Booknotes Reviews, 2001-2002 (Box 300, Folder 22)
  - American Writers II-Walter Lippmann, 2002 (Box 300, Folder 23)
  - American Writers II-Russell Kirk, 2002 (Box 301, Folder 1)
  - American Writers II-James Baldwin, 2002 (Box 301, Folder 2)
  - American Writers II-Jack Kerouac, 2002 (Box 301, Folder 3)
  - American Writers II-Ayn Rand Communications, 2002 (Box 301, Folder 4)
  - American Writers-Booker T. Washington and WEB DuBois, 2001 (Box 301, Folder 5)
  - American Writers-Black Elk, 2001 (Box 301, Folder 6)
  - American Writers-Willa Cather, 2001 (Box 301, Folder 7)
  - American Writers-Mark Twain, 2001 (Box 301, Folder 8)
  - American Writers-Abraham Lincoln, 2001 (Box 301, Folder 9)
  - American Writers-Mary Chesnut, 2001 (Box 301, Folder 10)
  - American Writers-Harriet Beecher Stowe, 2001 (Box 301, Folder 11)
  - American Writers-Nathaniel Hawthorne, May 21, 2001 (Box 301, Folder 12)
  - American Writers II-Elizabeth Cady Stanton, 2001 (Box 301, Folder 13)
  - American Writers-James Fenimore Cooper, 2002 (Box 301, Folder 14)
  - American Writers-Lewis and Clark, 2002 (Box 301, Folder 15)
  - American Writers-Thomas Jefferson/James Madison, 2002 (Box 301, Folder 16)
  - American Writers-Thomas Paine, 2002 (Box 301, Folder 17)
  - American Writers-Will Rogers, 2002 (Box 301, Folder 18)
  - FCC's Rules for Digital TV Service, 1997 (Box 301, Folder 19)
  - "Must-Carry" C-SPAN FAQs, 1998 (Box 301, Folder 20)
  - Subscriber Losses From "Must-Carry" Result, 1998 (Box 301, Folder 21)
  - Brian Lamb's Letter to Sen. McCain Regarding "Must-Carry,", 1998 (Box 301, Folder 22)
  - "Must-Carry" FCC Senate Debate, 1998 (Box 301, Folder 23)
  - Executive Board Website Updates, 2002-2003 (Box 301, Folder 24)
  - The Cable Center Space, 2004 (Box 301, Folder 25)
  - Denver Cable Learning Center, 2004 (Box 302, Folder 1)
  - Peter Hart Politicization Study, 2004 (Box 302, Folder 2)
  - FCC Reports for Broadcast Station, 1992-2001 (Box 302, Folder 3)
  - Bankruptcy Info, 1990-1993 (Box 302, Folder 4)
  - C-SPAN 25th Anniversary-Mail, 2004 (Box 302, Folder 5)
  - C-SPAN 25th Anniversary-Mail, 2004 (Box 302, Folder 6)
  - C-SPAN 25th Anniversary-Mail, 2004 (Box 302, Folder 7)
  - C-SPAN 25th Anniversary-Mail, 2004 (Box 302, Folder 8)
  - C-SPAN 20th Anniversary-Publications, 1999 (Box 302, Folder 9)
  - Radio Stations Info and Resolutions, 1997 (Box 302, Folder 10)
  - Two Maintenance Worker Notebooks, 1994-1995 (Box 302, Folder 11)
  - Supreme Court and Cameras, 1994-1995 (Box 303, Folder 1)
  - Press Releases, April-May 1999 (Box 303, Folder 2)
  - C-SPAN 25th Anniversary Press, 2004 (Box 303, Folder 3)
  - C-SPAN 25th Anniversary Press, 2004 (Box 303, Folder 4)
  - "C-SPAN Update" Newspaper, 1990 (Box 303, Folder 5)
  - Interview with Newt Gingrich Excerpts, circa 1990s (Box 303, Folder 6)
  - Political Coverage, 1998 (Box 303, Folder 7)
  - TV Cameras in Congress, 1994-1995 (Box 303, Folder 8)
  - A Tribute to Oprah Winfrey, 1992 (Box 303, Folder 9)
  - American Writers-Benjamin Franklin, 2001 (Box 303, Folder 10)
  - American Writers-William Bradford, March 14, 2002 (Box 303, Folder 11)
  - American Writers-General Research-Part 1, 2001 (Box 303, Folder 12)
  - American Writers-General Research-Part 2, 2001 (Box 303, Folder 13)
  - Booknotes 3 Brian Lamb Tour, 2001 (Box 303, Folder 14)
  - Booknotes 3 Sales Info, 2001 (Box 303, Folder 15)
  - Brian Lamb Correspondence: Booknotes Tour, 2001 (Box 303, Folder 16)
  - Brian Lamb Correspondence-Satellite TV, 2001 (Box 303, Folder 17)
  - Viewer Mail, 2003-2006 (Box 303, Folder 18)
  - Digital Must Carry-C-SPAN's Comments Before FCC, 1998 (Box 304, Folder 1)
  - Digital Must Carry-C-SPAN Reply Comments, circa 1990s (Box 304, Folder 2)
  - Digital Must Carry Newsclippings, 1998 (Box 304, Folder 3)
  - Digital Must Carry-FCC Appointments, 1998 (Box 304, Folder 4)
  - Digital Must Carry-FCC Rule Making Session, 1998 (Box 304, Folder 5)
  - Digital Must Carry-NCTA Timeline to Transition, circa 1990s (Box 304, Folder 6)
  - Digital Must Carry-NCTA Pocket, July 1998 (Box 304, Folder 7)
  - NAB-Fritz Letter, 1998 (Box 304, Folder 8)
  - Hagan and Hartson LLP, Digital Must Carry Memo, 1998 (Box 304, Folder 9)
  - CATA Cable-Articles on Digital Must Carry, 1998 (Box 304, Folder 10)
  - Paper Cut-Out of John Splaine's Head-History Consultant for C-SPAN Programs-Head, circa 2000 (Box 304, Folder 11)
  - Charleston SC Calendar Sent to Brian Lamb, 2009 (Box 304, Folder 12)
  - Mail Received by Brian Lamb, 2000s (Box 304, Folder 13)
  - Pamphlets and Publications, 2000s (Box 304, Folder 14)
  - Personnel List, circa 2000s (Box 304, Folder 15)
  - Cable in the Classroom-10 Year Packet, 2000 (Box 304, Folder 16)
  - Brian Lamb's America Packet, 1999 (Box 304, Folder 17)
  - Students and Leaders, 2004 (Box 304, Folder 18)
  - 25th Anniversary Materials, 2004-2006 (Box 304, Folder 19)
  - Educational Supply Locations/Directory, 2000 (Box 305, Folder 1)
  - Classroom Support Materials, 1999 (Box 305, Folder 2)
  - Marketing Communication, 2000s (Box 305, Folder 3)
  - Cable Labs Specs, 2000 (Box 305, Folder 4)
  - Product Order Forms-Books, 2000s (Box 305, Folder 5)
  - C-SPAN Publications Including Presidents Timeline, 2000s (Box 305, Folder 6)
  - Insik/Offsite Storage, 2005 (Box 305, Folder 7)
  - The Cable Center, Spring 2006 (Box 305, Folder 8)
  - George Mason University Communications, 2000s (Box 305, Folder 9)
  - The History Factory Communications, 2005 (Box 305, Folder 10)
  - Digitization Estimates, 2000s (Box 305, Folder 11)
  - Coporate Archive and Inventory, 2000s (Box 305, Folder 12)
  - Intranet Packets, 2000 (Box 305, Folder 13)
  - Transcript of Brian Lamb Interview, 2003 (Box 305, Folder 14)
  - Brand Resonance and Involvement Powerpoint, 2004 (Box 305, Folder 15)
  - Holding Materials: Booknotes, Mail, Surveys, 2000s (Box 305, Folder 16)
  - 25th Anniversary Packets and Info, 2004 (Box 305, Folder 17)
  - 25th Anniversary Viewer Content and Essays, 2004 (Box 305, Folder 18)
  - 25th Anniversary Viewer Content and Essays, 2004 (Box 305, Folder 19)
  - Early Press and Employee Info, circa 2000s (Box 306, Folder 1)
  - Comics and Political Cartoons, 1990s (Box 306, Folder 2)
  - Milestones in C-SPAN History, 1970s-1999 (Box 306, Folder 3)
  - TV News and Public Affairs Survey, 2004 (Box 306, Folder 4)
  - Letters From Senators, Representatives, and President George Bush, 2005 (Box 306, Folder 5)
  - Info Packets for White House and Congress, 1990s-2000 (Box 306, Folder 6)
  - C-SPAN Company Info, 2004 (Box 306, Folder 7)
  - American Writers Printed Pieces and Press Kit, 2002 (Box 306, Folder 8)
  - C-SPAN Internship Info, 2009 (Box 306, Folder 9)
  - Election '96 C-SPAN Branded Items, 1996 (Box 306, Folder 10)
  - Brian Lamb's Awards Including Presidential Medal of Freedom, 1990s-2000s (Box 306, Folder 11)
  - Campaign 2000 and 2008 Fact Sheets, 2000-2008 (Box 306, Folder 12)
  - Booknotes #1-Tour Locations, 1997 (Box 306, Folder 13)
  - Presidential and Congressional Pamphlets/Memos, 2000s (Box 306, Folder 14)
  - TV and Telephone Primers, 1990s (Box 306, Folder 15)
  - Phone Call Lists-Brian Lamb-Part 1, 1994-1995 (Box 307, Folder 1)
  - Phone Call Lists-Brian Lamb-Part 2, 1994-1995 (Box 307, Folder 2)
  - Journalist's Letters to Brian Lamb-Part 1, 1994-1995 (Box 307, Folder 3)
  - Journalist's Letters to Brian Lamb-Part 2, 1994-1995 (Box 307, Folder 4)
  - Industry Mail Received by Brian Lamb-Part 1, 1994-1995 (Box 307, Folder 5)
  - Industry Mail Received by Brian Lamb-Part 2, 1994-1995 (Box 307, Folder 6)
  - Mail Received by Brian Lamb, 1994 (Box 308, Folder 1)
  - Nixon Broadcast Responses-Part 1, 1994 (Box 308, Folder 2)
  - Nixon Broadcast Responses-Part 2, 1994 (Box 308, Folder 3)
  - Nixon Broadcast Responses-Part 3, 1994 (Box 308, Folder 4)
  - Nixon Broadcast Responses-Part 4, 1994 (Box 308, Folder 5)
  - Viewer Mail, 1996 (Box 308, Folder 6)
  - Viewer Mail, 1994-1995 (Box 308, Folder 7)
  - Everybody Wins When Adults Read with Children, 1995 (Box 308, Folder 8)
  - Intellectual Property Lawyer's Packet, circa 1990s (Box 308, Folder 9)
  - Chain Letter Sent to Brian Lamb, 1995 (Box 308, Folder 10)
  - Forte Design Consultancy Packet, 1995 (Box 308, Folder 11)
  - Election Coverage Publications, 1996 (Box 308, Folder 12)
  - Letters from Collegiate Sources, 1990s-2000s (Box 309, Folder 1)
  - Sign-In Books From C-SPAN Office, 1990-2000 (Box 309, Folder 2)
  - Broadband and Affiliate Sales Memos, 1995 (Box 309, Folder 3)
  - Viewer Services Memos, 1994 (Box 309, Folder 4)
  - Richard Ben-Veniste Interview, 1995 (Box 309, Folder 5)
  - Programming Lineup Changes, 1994 (Box 309, Folder 6)
  - Education and Marketing Packets, 1994 (Box 309, Folder 7)
  - Ken Starr Interview, 1995 (Box 309, Folder 8)
  - C-SPAN Digest and '92 Bags, 1992-1993 (Box 309, Folder 9)
  - Guest Sign-In Books, 1988-1992 (Box 309, Folder 10)
  - Finance Procedure and Guidelines, May 1993 (Box 309, Folder 11)
  - Sample Stationary, 1984-1996 (Box 309, Folder 12)
  - Election 1996 Press Kit (Box 310, Folder 1)
  - Draper Hill Cartoon Book (Signed), 1996 (Box 310, Folder 2)
  - Political Cartoons Made by 7th Graders, 1995 (Box 310, Folder 3)
  - Industry Communication, 1990s (Box 310, Folder 4)
  - Rich Reed DA Synthesis Communication, 1996 (Box 310, Folder 5)
  - Industry Communication, 1990s (Box 310, Folder 6)
  - Industry Communications, 1990s (Box 310, Folder 7)
  - Industry Communications, 1990s (Box 310, Folder 8)
  - Journalists Letters Received by Brian Lamb, 1994-1996 (Box 310, Folder 9)
  - The Journey of a Butterfly-A Viewer's Guide, circa 1990s (Box 310, Folder 10)
  - Robert E. Frye, circa 1990 (Box 310, Folder 11)
  - Marketing Proposal, June 1989 (Box 311, Folder 1)
  - Industry Correspondence and Memos, 1990s (Box 311, Folder 2)
  - George Shea Letters and "Works,", 1990s (Box 311, Folder 3)
  - America's Patriotic Poems and Prose, George Shea and "What Really Happened at The Battle of Little Big Horn,", circa 1990s (Box 311, Folder 4)
  - Commercial Packets Sent to Lea Anne Long, 1990s (Box 311, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Newspapers-Part 1, 1980-1990s (Box 311, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Newspapers-Part 2, 1980-1990s (Box 311, Folder 7)
  - Newspapers and Magazines, 1980s-1990s (Box 312, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers and Magazines, 1990 (Box 312, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence from Ashly H. Woo to Lamb, June-July 9, 1999 (Box 312, Folder 3)
  - Letter from Sam Garrett to Lamb and Corresponding Paper, January 17, 2000, December 6, 1999 (Box 312, Folder 4)
  - Thank You Letter from Olivia J. Johnson to Lamb, June 16, 1999 (Box 312, Folder 5)
  - Eagle Scout Announcement for Cris Gualberto to Lamb, May 28, 1999 (Box 312, Folder 6)
  - "Counting Quality"-Ursinus College-Two Copies, circa 2000 (Box 312, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence from Georgia Sorenson, Ph. D. to Lamb, January 14, 2000 (Box 312, Folder 8)
  - The James MacGregor Burns Academy of Leadership Pamphlet, circa 2000 (Box 312, Folder 9)
  - Letter from James E. Pontuso to Lamb, March 6, 2000 (Box 312, Folder 10)
  - Letters to Lea Anne Long and Lamb from Donna Briggs, circa 2000 (Box 312, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence from Lillie M. Fears, Ph. D. to Long and Lamb, September 1, 3, 1998 (Box 312, Folder 12)
  - Letter from Julian Zelizer to Lamb, December 16, 1998 (Box 312, Folder 13)
  - Letter from Kyle Longley to Lamb, January 5, 1999 (Box 312, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence from Don Corrigan to Lamb, June 1999 (Box 312, Folder 15)
  - Letter from Andrew J. Polsky to Lamb, June 6, 1999 (Box 312, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence from William B. Allen to Lamb, April 10, 2000 (Box 312, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence and Graduation Announcement from Sam Garrett to Lamb, May 2000 (Box 312, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence from Donald J. Modica-Columbia Journal of Literature and Art-to Lamb, January 15, 2000 (Box 312, Folder 19)
  - Letter from Mary E. and Charles R. Reina to Lamb, May 27, 2000 (Box 312, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence from Robert Schmul to Lamb, May 21, 1999, October 1999 (Box 312, Folder 21)
  - Letter from Jennifer Lynn Purcell (UCSB) to Lamb, October 22, 1999 (Box 312, Folder 22)
  - Letter from Roger H. Martin (Randolph-Macon College) to Lamb, November 19, 1999 (Box 312, Folder 23)
  - Letter from Barry Bernstein Bradford (Adlai Stevenson High School, IL) to Lamb, September 29, 1999 (Box 312, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence from David A. Caputo (Hunter) to Lamb, November 23, 1999 (Box 312, Folder 25)
  - Thank You Note from Aaron Longo to Lamb, circa 2000 (Box 312, Folder 26)
  - Letter from Stephen Gilroy (Manhasset Public Schools) to Lamb, circa 2000 (Box 312, Folder 27)
  - Letter from Nelson W. Polsby (UC Berkeley) to Lamb, January 11, 2000 (Box 312, Folder 28)
  - Letter from Christine Martin (Dean of West Virginia University), January 14, 2000 (Box 312, Folder 29)
  - Letter from Philip S. Alito to Lamb, July 21, 1999 (Box 312, Folder 30)
  - Letter from Denney G. French (Center Grove Community School Corporation) to Lamb, February 21, 2000 (Box 312, Folder 31)
  - Letter from Meena Bose (Asst. Professor Hofstra University) to Lamb, January 26, 2000 (Box 312, Folder 32)
  - Thank You Note from Annie Glanville, circa November 16, 1999 (Box 312, Folder 33)
  - Letter from Margaret Galligan, Ph. D. (Penn State), December 15, 1999 (Box 312, Folder 34)
  - Letter from David Burton (Saint Joseph's University) to Lamb, September 9, 1999 (Box 312, Folder 35)
  - Printed E-Mail Correspondence from Jackson Foote to Lamb, September 21, 1999, March 7, 31, 2000 (Box 312, Folder 36)
  - Birthday Card to Lamb, circa 1999 (Box 312, Folder 37)
  - Letter from Jane Hall (American University) to Lamb, September 28, 1999 (Box 312, Folder 38)
  - Letter from Gil Troy (History Dept. Chairman, McGill University) to Lamb, February 12, 1998 (Box 312, Folder 39)
  - Letter from John Johnson to Lamb (Arizona State University), October 22, 1998 (Box 312, Folder 40)
  - Page of "C-SPAN in the Classroom News," Volume I. Issue 2, Fall 1998 (Box 312, Folder 41)
  - Note from Marcella "Marci" B. Woodman (Pennichuck High School, NH) to Lamb, Thank You Note from [Illegible], November 16, 1998, circa 1999 (Box 312, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence from Robert "Bob" Schmuhl to Lamb, June 27, 29, 1999 (Box 312, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence from Glennette Tilley Turner to Lamb, July 9, 1999 (Box 312, Folder 44)
  - Note from Sally Souder to Lamb, November 17, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence from James E. Hinish, Jr. (Regent University) to Lamb, March 6, April 24, 2000 (Box 313, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence from Victor E. Ferrall, Jr. and Michael J. Koss (Beloit College), June 10, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 3)
  - Letter from Janice Jose to Lamb, June 8, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 4)
  - Letter from Frances Wood to Lamb, June 16, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 5)
  - Letter from Donus D. Roberts (Watertown Senior High School, SD) to Lamb, March 10, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 6)
  - Letter from George B. Stow, Ph. D. (La Salle University, PA) to Lamb, April 14, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 7)
  - Note from John Frank to Lamb, July 30, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 8)
  - Thank You Letter to Lamb, July 27, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 9)
  - Letter from Diana B. Carlin, Ph. D. (University of Kansas) to Lamb, April 2, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence from Maddy Steinhart to Lamb, November 11, 13, 1998 (Box 313, Folder 11)
  - Letter from Marian Nagler to Lamb, December 10, 1998 (Box 313, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence from Vane Scott to Lamb on "Vane Scott's 'Many Faces of Old Glory',", March 27, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 13)
  - Letter from James E. Hinish, Jr. (Regent University) to Lamb, April 14, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence from Sanford Ungar, Dean, American University, November 30, 1998 (Box 313, Folder 15)
  - Letter from Steve [Illegible] (Ball State University, IN) to Lamb, February 5, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 16)
  - Letter from James E. Hinish, Jr. (Regent University, VA) to Lamb, February 16, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 17)
  - Note from [Illegible] (Southern Illinois University) to Lamb, circa 1999 (Box 313, Folder 18)
  - Thank You Note from Joshua Peet to Lamb, February 22, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 19)
  - Note from Russ Lundgren to Lamb, April 28, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence from Jackie Andren to Lamb, circa 1999 (Box 313, Folder 21)
  - Letter from Ray Beery (GMU) to Lamb, March 20, 2000 (Box 313, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence from Alan Merten to Lamb, March 24, April 5, 2000 (Box 313, Folder 23)
  - Christmas Card with Photos of Lamb, February 4, 2000, November 1999 (Box 313, Folder 24)
  - Printed E-Mail from Joe S. Foote (Southern Illinois University) to Lamb, March 23, 2000 (Box 313, Folder 25)
  - Memorandum from Benjamin Edwards to Lamb, May 8, 2000 (Box 313, Folder 26)
  - Letter from Douglas "Doug" Anderson (Penn State) to Lamb, May 24, 2000 (Box 313, Folder 27)
  - Letter from Andrew Mauck (Knox College, IL) to Lamb, May 26, 2001 (Box 313, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence from John Strassburger (Ursinus College, PA) to Lamb, May 24, 2000 (Box 313, Folder 29)
  - Letter from Mary Elizabeth Sperry (DC Area Phi Beta Kappa Assoc.) to Long, August 3, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence from Stephen C. Moberly (Indiana Retired Teachers Union) to Lamb, October 15, 1999, Fall 1994 (Box 313, Folder 31)
  - The Indianapolis Star Article "Humble Contrarian" Profiling Lamb, August 24, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 32)
  - Thank You Notes to Lamb and C-SPAN Staff, circa 2000, February 29, 2000 (Box 313, Folder 33)
  - The Advertiser-Tribune Article "TV announces Year 2000 commencement speaker" Profiling Lamb, March 6, 2000 (Box 313, Folder 34)
  - Letter from Thomas "Tom" S. Ulen (University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign) to Lamb, January 17, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 35)
  - Letter from Todd Bouldin (University of Tennessee, College of Law) to Lamb, February 13, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 36)
  - Letter from Doug Brinkley (The Eisenhower Center for American Studies) to Lamb, February 11, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 37)
  - Printed E-Mail from Sandra Markle to Lamb, November 2, 1998 (Box 313, Folder 38)
  - Letter from James N. Giglio (Southwest Missouri State Univeristy) to Lamb, November 16, 1998 (Box 313, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence from Robert "Bob" J. Greene to Lamb, Includes Article from Forward, December 22, 18, 1998 (Box 313, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence to Long on The January Series of Calvin College, July 31, 1998 (Box 313, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence from Gordon J. DiRenzo (University of Delaware) to Lamb, September 29, 1998 (Box 313, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence from John Strassburger (Ursinus College, PA) to Lamb, August 18, 1998 (Box 313, Folder 43)
  - Letter from Ralph J. Begleiter (University of Delaware) to Lamb, August 24, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 44)
  - Employee Mail, 1995-1996 (Box 313, Folder 45)
  - Employee Mail, 1997 (Box 313, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence from Veronica D. DiConti (American University) to Lamb, September 28, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 47)
  - Letter from Kathryn Falk (Virginia Cable Telecommunications Association President) to Lamb-Includes Photographs of Lamb's Attendance of a VCTA Banquet, December 11, 1998 (Box 313, Folder 48)
  - Itinerary-Chicago/Omaha/Kansas City/San Antonio, November 1-5, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 49)
  - Letter from Thomas E. Patterson (Harvard University) to Lamb, January 14, 2000 (Box 313, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence from Neil J. McElroy (Lafayette College) to Lamb, July 12, September 6, October 1, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 51)
  - Letter from Kathleen M. Donnelly to Lamb, December 29, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 52)
  - Letter from Michele Maiullo (Free Public Library of Hasbrouck Heights, NJ) to Lamb, November 30, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 53)
  - Letter from William L. Pak (Purdue Univeristy) to Lamb, December 22, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence from W.L. Helmantoler to Lamb, January 30, 2000, February 5, 2000 (Box 313, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence to Long from Stephen C. Moberly (Indiana Retired Teachers Association), January 14, 2000 (Box 313, Folder 56)
  - Letters and Photos from Ana Leilani Kaahanui (Borders Book-Music-Cafe) to Lamb, circa 2000 (Box 313, Folder 57)
  - Letter from William "Bill" Martin to Lamb, November 26, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence from Lake Forest College, IL to Lamb, November 6, 11, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 59)
  - Letter from Jeffrey R. Biggs (American Political Science Association) to Lamb, December 17, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence from Jacquelyn Beauregard Dillman (Newport Beach Public Library Foundation Board, CA) to Lamb, September 13, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 61)
  - Letter from Charles Chieffe to Lamb, November 12, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 62)
  - Letter from Judith Lieberman to Lamb, February 22, 2000 (Box 313, Folder 63)